Lesson 13.
Amber comes over to bake cookies.
Ted's girlfriend, Amber, comes over to help with the cookies.
Amber has experienced baking cookies from a former job.
Susan leaves the kitchen so they can work better.
Mom, Amber is here to lend a hand with the cookies.
Hi, Amber. Nice to see you again.
Good to see you too, Mrs. Johnson.
That's an interesting hairstyle.
Thanks. I'm glad you think it's cool.
Blue hair is all the rage this season.
Well, I'm going to take a break now and let you kids take over.
Don't worry, Mom. Your business isn't good hands with Amber.
She really knows her stuff.
That's true. I used to work at Miss Fields cookies in the mall.
You don't work there anymore?
No, I got fired.
I have a real sweet tooth and they told me I was eating too many cookies.
Well, I'm sure you haven't lost your touch.
It might be a bit out of practice.
Mom, you can watch Amber bake if you want.
You might pick up a few tricks to the trade.
Yes, feel free.
As a singer, I'm used to performing before an audience.
Thanks, but I'm going to get out of the way.
You know what they say.
Too many cooks spoil the broth.
Will I see you later tonight?
Yes, I'll be back in a few hours.
Mom, why don't you just call it a night and go to bed.
You've been working your tail off all day.